good afternoon Hello From Ukraine, the
добрый день Здравствуйте Из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky, where Well, I realized that it’s
город Хмельницкого откуда Ну я понял что
not from Russia that your flag is upside down. I’m from
не из России у вас флаг переверн Я из
Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky. You are from
Украины город Хмельницкий Вы откуда
Moscow Russia, namely Moscow or the
Москва Россия именно Москва или
Moscow region,
Подмосковье
they wanted to say something about the flag.
что-то там хотели про флаг сказать
there were two forms and
было две формы был и желтоблакетный на
yellow-bluque on yellow on top the bouquet was blue yellow
желтый сверху букет был синий желтый
blue on top
синий сверху
nowhere is the
нигде
documentation fixed what
документациях не фиксируются какая
algorithm the sequence is the
алгоритм последовательность это
documentation is called the Constitution the
документация называется Конституция там
state is written there changed in the
прописано государство поменяли в
Constitution, see in 96 When
Конституции смотрите в 96 году Когда
they adopted the Constitution Yes there is a prescribed
приняли в Конституцию Да там прописанный
flag That's exactly the one that was blue
флаг Вот именно такой который был синий
on top  yellow from below What is the difference
сверху желтый снизу А в чем разница
why they changed it, they just didn’t change it, they
почему поменяли просто не меняли так
accepted it since 91 Independence Day 1,
приняли с 91 года Дня Независимости 1
this flag was adopted by us, they didn’t change it, they
этот флаг был принят у нас не меняли
just made a mistake, it’s just that someone
просто ошиблись это вам просто кто-то по
told you some stories that he
рассказывал какие-то байки что он там
changed something there
что-то меняли
I saw  even the films are old
Я видел даже фильмы старый
No
Нет
, the whole world already knows
уже весь мир знает
about good Well, somehow you approve of Oh  what
о добре Ну как-то одобряете по О каком
century I don’t remember this film was generally the
веке я не помню этот фильм был вообще
Stone Age there The Middle Ages in the Stone
каменный век там Средние века в Каменном
Age
веке
Ukrainians were
украинцы были
always there was
всегда
no one you were
никого не было вы были
first Ukrainian
сначала украинец
first Ukrainians appeared
сначала появились украинцы
and therefore First there was the sea below
и поэтому Сначала был внизу море
you know why Russia has yellow
знаете почему у России сверху желтый
boys with blue shirts on top dominates
пацаны с синими рубашками доминирует над
suckers  with yellow t-shirts I understand Glory to
лохами с желтыми футболками понял Слава
Ukraine
Украине
[laughter]
[смех]
put a plus sign on the joke itself cool
поставьте плюсик прикол самому классно
so it’s real
так вот реально
[laughter]
[смех]
starting there it
начиная там это
’s a
мочах
class damn
класс блин
if someone didn’t subscribe after that you
если кто-то не подписался после этого вы
bastard them you soulless
[__] их ты бездушный
damn for such a declining in
блин за такие преклонный
short friends the topic is cool
короче друзья тема прикольно